{
    "id": "emi",
    "name": "Coding Standards ",
    "description": "So, please check your level of learning in Coding Standards section !!",
    "passPercentage": "90",
    "mode": "wizard",
    "questions":[
        {
            "id": 1,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "1. All reusable code should be move to Tools/Utility class.",
            "options": [
                {"id": 1, "text":  "True"},
                {"id": 2, "text":  "False"}
            ],
            "answer": 1,
            "score": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "2. Do not eliminate unnecessary repeated method calls from loops.",
            "options": [
                {"id": 1, "text":  "True"},
                {"id": 2, "text":  "False"}
            ],
            "answer": 2,
            "score": 1
        },        
        {
            "id": 3,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "3. Avoid unnecessary casts.",
            "options": [
                {"id": 1, "text":  "True"},
                {"id": 2, "text":  "False"}
            ],
            "answer": 1,
            "score": 1
        },        
        {
            "id": 4,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "4. Eliminate repeated casts by casting once and holding the cast item in a correctly typed variable.",
            "options": [
                {"id": 1, "text":  "True"},
                {"id": 2, "text":  "False"}
            ],
            "answer": 1,
            "score": 1
        },        
        {
            "id": 5,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "5. Have null checks to avoid the possibility of _______.",
            "options": [
                {"id": 1, "text": "Null Pointer Exception"},
                {"id": 2, "text": "IO Exception"},
                {"id": 3, "text": "Arithmetic Exception"},
                {"id": 4, "text": "Runtime Exception"}
            ],
            "answer": 1,
            "score": 1
        },  	
        {
            "id": 6,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "2. Which of the following is a proper constant name ?",
            "options": [
                {"id": 1, "text": "NUMBER_TWO"},
                {"id": 2, "text": "TWENTY_TWO"},
                {"id": 3, "text": "MAX_COUNT"},
                {"id": 4, "text": "All the above"}
            ],
            "answer": 3,
            "score": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 7,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "7. Which is the best way to propagate error details from a function to caller ?",
            "options": [
                {"id": 1, "text": "Use Error codes as integers"},
                {"id": 2, "text": "Return boolen return value & pass  error details as parameter"},
                {"id": 3, "text": "Use exceptions"},
                {"id": 4, "text": "Combination of 1 & 2"}
            ],
            "answer": 4,
            "score": 1
        },      
        {
            "id": 8,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "8. NCSS Method Count - Searches for methods with more than ___ lines of code.",
            "options": [
                {"id": 1, "text": "25"},
                {"id": 2, "text": "35"},
                {"id": 3, "text": "50"},
                {"id": 4, "text": "80"}
            ],
            "answer": 3,
            "score": 1
        },        
        {
            "id": 9,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "9. Along with exceptions what all details need to passed ?",
            "options": [
                {"id": 1, "text": "Create informative error messages and pass them along with your exceptions"},
                {"id": 2, "text": "Pass the entire stack trace"},
                {"id": 3, "text": "No need to pass any details"},
                {"id": 4, "text": "Only logging is required during exceptions"}
            ],
            "answer": 1,
            "score": 1
        },   
        {
            "id": 10,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "10. Functions or methods should do only one thing.",
            "options": [
                {"id": 1, "text":  "True"},
                {"id": 2, "text":  "False"}
            ],
            "answer": 1,
            "score": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 11,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "11. Are custom logic written instead of using available API methods ?",
            "options": [
                {"id": 1, "text":  "True"},
                {"id": 2, "text":  "False"}
            ],
            "answer": 1,
            "score": 1
        }       
    ]
}
    